(Penny:)Yeah, get it, girl.
(Amy:)It's not what you think.
(Leonard:)I feel like
I pulled something.
(Leonard:)Why didn't you tell me to stop?
(Penny:)Even more not
what you think.
(Sheldon:)I don't know
if I can make it
(Amy:)through five weeks
living with him.
(Leonard:)If you ever need a break,
the owner of the train store
(Leonard:)will let you leave him there
while you get a coffee.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Good morning.
(Sheldon:)See? I didn't knock,
but it's fine.
(Sheldon:)I didn't knock, but it's fine.
I didn't knock, but it's fine.
(Sheldon:)So, how is everyone?
(Amy:)Miserable and exhausted.
(Sheldon:)Really? I slept great.
(Amy:)Well, I didn't,
and it's your fault.
(Sheldon:)How? You had the whole floor
to yourself.
(Amy:)Sheldon, maybe living together
is a bad idea.
Well... Yeah, but what kind
of scientists would we be,
(Sheldon:)drawing a conclusion
after only 12 hours of data?